lawtomatic.com 2011-12-27

# Lawtomatic | Law On Your Terms! Privacy Policy

## 1\. Security

We provide the use of a secure server to all users of the site. The secure server uses encryption software to secure all information sent to us. All user data collected by Lawtomatic.com is accessible only by authorized users. We will make every attempt to maintain the security and integrity of the information submitted to this site. 

Access to some content and services is password protected. Please make sure that you protect the password of your account in order to prevent another party from viewing the information you submitted. The information shared between and attorney and a client is considered privileged and confidential. If someone obtains access to your password they will have access to that information which can have adverse effects to the outcome of your legal issue.

An important part of the security used on our site is the use of unique passwords associated with your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information, including account information and Privileged Information. Do not give your password out to anybody including any person claiming they are from Lawtomatic.com. If you believe that someone may have obtained access to your password please contact us immediately at info@Lawtomatic.com and change your password.

## 2\. Data Collection

When you register, you provide us with various kinds of personal information such as your name, mailing and e-mail address as well as demographic information such as geographical area. If you are an attorney, you also provide us with information about your practice as well as your bar registration number and the year you were admitted to the bar. When you post a legal issue you are providing information specifically relating to the nature of that issue. The information you provide is necessary for our service to function properly. 

In addition to personal information, we collect aggregate information relating to site traffic such as the number of unique visitors, the origin of those visits, page views, the number of attorneys registered on the site, the number of cases posted and in which areas of law they were posted. This aggregate information only to users of the site as a whole and is not comprised of any specific personal information. 

We may make use of cookie technology in order to provide you with a more personalized and efficient service. Cookies are small pieces of information that are sent to the hard drive by the Web server for record keeping purposes. The information can be retrieved by the same Web server in order to help you avoid having to input the same data every time you visit the site. In addition, cookies allow us to track usage of the site to determine those areas of the site which are most useful or popular. Cookies may not be used to read any information, personal or otherwise, from your computer other than that information which corresponds to the particular Web site contained in its cookie. You can reset your browser either to notify you when you receive a cookie or to refuse to accept cookies. Certain areas of the site may not function properly if you refuse to accept cookies. 

## 3\. Use of Data

The data you provide is used to register you on our site and makes it possible for us to send you responses to your posted legal matter. We will not disclose any personal information to any third party. The aggregate information we collect about site usage may be provided to third parties but this will not in any way divulge any personal information about any of our customers. 

We may also send you informational e-mails regarding various products or services that may be of interest to you. These e-mails will not be sent unless you give us permission to do so during the registration process.

## 4\. Confidentiality

We will not disclose any information you provide regarding your legal matter to any third party. This is information that is held in confidence between a participating attorney and a customer as a result of the attorney-client relationship including, without limitation, queries submitted by prospective clients and answers provided by member attorneys to those parties. However, Lawtomatic.com may, under certain circumstances be compelled to disclose this type of information pursuant to a judicial or administrative order or by an applicable statute. In the event that any information is compelled by any legal process, we will use reasonable efforts under the circumstances to notify the persons identified of such an order so that they will have to opportunity to take the appropriate legal actions. 

## 5\. Records

Parties seeking legal services will only be permitted to access the legal matter that they posted and the corresponding response by the attorneys interested in handling their matter. Participating attorneys and their firms will only be permitted to access the posted matter to which they responded and their response to that matter. Any posted legal matter and any response to a posted legal matter may be stored in a secure database. However, Lawtomatic.com may delete any and all copies of the aforementioned data at any time in its sole discretion. Since Lawtomatic.com is merely a forum, we will not serve as a keeper or custodian of any records for any party. Therefore, each party whether they are an attorney or a client will have sole responsibility for making and storing copies of any information submitted to Lawtomatic.com. 

## 6\. Consent and Changes to the Policy

By registering on the website, you consent to the collection, storage and use of this data by Lawtomatic.com. Lawtomatic.com will not use any personal information provided by you for any purpose than to contact you via e-mail of any responses to your posted legal matter. Any changes made to this policy will be posted on this page. Use of the site after those changes are posted will constitute consent to the new policy.
